{"Questions": { "Question #110 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company is planning to migrate from on-premises to the AWS Cloud. Which AWS tool or service provides detailed reports on estimated cost savings after migration?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator", "B. Cost Explorer", "C. AWS Budgets", "CORRECT:D. AWS Migration Hub"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/migrationhub/latest/ug/hub-api.pdf (26)","discussions": "16"}, "Question #111 Topic 2":{ "question":"What can assist in evaluating an application for migration to the cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Trusted Advisor", "B. AWS Professional Services", "C. AWS Systems Manager", "CORRECT:D. AWS Partner Network (APN)", "E. AWS Secrets Manager"],"explanation": "","discussions": "10"}, "Question #112 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service helps users meet contractual and regulatory compliance requirements for data security by using dedicated hardware appliances within the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Secrets Manager", "CORRECT:B. AWS CloudHSM", "C. AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)", "D. AWS Directory Service"],"explanation": "The AWS CloudHSM service helps you meet corporate, contractual, and regulatory compliance requirements for data security by using dedicated Hardware Security Module (HSM) instances within the AWS cloud. AWS and AWS Marketplace partners offer a variety of solutions for protecting sensitive data within the AWS platform, but for some applications and data subject to contractual or regulatory mandates for managing cryptographic keys, additional protection may be necessary. CloudHSM complements existing data protection solutions and allows you to protect your encryption keys within HSMs that are designed and validated to government standards for secure key management. CloudHSM allows you to securely generate, store, and manage cryptographic keys used for data encryption in a way that keys are accessible only by you. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudhsm/faqs/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #113 Topic 2":{ "question":"Under the AWS shared responsibility model, the customer manages which of the following? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Decommissioning of physical storage devices", "CORRECT:B. Security group and ACL configuration", "C. Patch management of an Amazon RDS instance operating system", "D. Controlling physical access to data centers", "CORRECT:E. Patch management of an Amazon EC2 instance operating system"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.whizlabs.com/blog/aws-security-shared-responsibility/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #114 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service is suitable for an event-driven workload?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon EC2", "CORRECT:B. AWS Elastic Beanstalk", "C. AWS Lambda", "D. Amazon Lumberyard"],"explanation": "An easy-to-use service for deploying and scaling web applications and web services developed in a number of programming languages. You can configure event notifications for your Elastic Beanstalk environment so that notable events can be automatically published to an SNS topic, then pushed to topic subscribers.As an example, you may use this event-driven architecture to coordinate your continuous integration pipeline (such as Jenkins CI). That way, whenever an environment is created, Elastic Beanstalk publishes this event to an SNS topic, which triggers a subscribing Lambda function, which then kicks off a CI job against your newly created Elastic Beanstalk environment. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/compute/event-driven-computing-with-amazon-sns-compute-storage-database-and-networking-services/","discussions": "14"}, "Question #115 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is a value proposition of the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. AWS is responsible for security in the AWS Cloud", "CORRECT:B. No long-term contract is required", "C. Provision new servers in days", "D. AWS manages user applications in the AWS Cloud"],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-whitepaper-business-value-of-aws.pdf","discussions": "1"}, "Question #116 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is a characteristic of Amazon S3 cross-region replication?", "answers":[ "A. Both source and destination S3 buckets must have versioning disabled", "B. The source and destination S3 buckets cannot be in different AWS Regions", "CORRECT:C. S3 buckets configured for cross-region replication can be owned by a single AWS account or by different accounts", "D. The source S3 bucket owner must have the source and destination AWS Regions disabled for their account"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/replication.html","discussions": "2"}, "Question #117 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is a user responsible for when running an application in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Managing physical hardware", "B. Updating the underlying hypervisor", "C. Providing a list of users approved for data center access", "CORRECT:D. Managing application software updates"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "7"}, "Question #118 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company that does business online needs to quickly deliver new functionality in an iterative manner, minimizing the time to market. Which AWS Cloud feature can provide this?", "answers":[ "A. Elasticity", "B. High availability", "CORRECT:C. Agility", "D. Reliability"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/devops/partner-solutions/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #119 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which features or services can be used to monitor costs and expenses for an AWS account? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Cost and Usage report", "B. AWS product pages", "C. AWS Simple Monthly Calculator", "CORRECT:D. Billing alerts and Amazon CloudWatch alarms", "E. AWS Price List API"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/monitor_estimated_charges_with_cloudwatch.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #120 Topic 2":{ "question":"Amazon Route 53 enables users to:", "answers":[ "A. encrypt data in transit", "CORRECT:B. register DNS domain names", "C. generate and manage SSL certificates", "D. establish a dedicated network connection to AWS"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/Route53/latest/DeveloperGuide/Welcome.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #121 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service helps identify malicious or unauthorized activities in AWS accounts and workloads?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Rekognition", "B. AWS Trusted Advisor", "CORRECT:C. Amazon GuardDuty", "D. Amazon CloudWatch"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/guardduty/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #122 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company wants to try a third-party ecommerce solution before deciding to use it long term. Which AWS service or tool will support this effort?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Marketplace", "B. AWS Partner Network (APN)", "C. AWS Managed Services", "D. AWS Service Catalog"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2019/09/aws-marketplace-easier-to-find-solutions-from-aws-console/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #123 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service is a managed NoSQL database?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Redshift", "CORRECT:B. Amazon DynamoDB", "C. Amazon Aurora", "D. Amazon RDS for MariaDB"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #124 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service should be used to create a billing alarm?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Trusted Advisor", "B. AWS CloudTrail", "CORRECT:C. Amazon CloudWatch", "D. Amazon QuickSight"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/monitor_estimated_charges_with_cloudwatch.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #125 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company is hosting a web application in a Docker container on Amazon EC2. AWS is responsible for which of the following tasks?", "answers":[ "A. Scaling the web application and services developed with Docker", "B. Provisioning or scheduling containers to run on clusters and maintain their availability", "CORRECT:C. Performing hardware maintenance in the AWS facilities that run the AWS Cloud", "D. Managing the guest operating system, including updates and security patches"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/tutorials/deploy-docker-containers/","discussions": "8"}, "Question #126 Topic 2":{ "question":"Users are reporting latency when connecting to a website with a global customer base. Which AWS service will improve the customer experience by reducing latency?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon CloudFront", "B. AWS Direct Connect", "C. Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling", "D. AWS Transit Gateway"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/tutorials/deliver-content-faster/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #127 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which actions represent best practices for using AWS IAM? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Configure a strong password policy", "B. Share the security credentials among users of AWS accounts who are in the same Region", "C. Use access keys to log in to the AWS Management Console", "CORRECT:D. Rotate access keys on a regular basis", "E. Avoid using IAM roles to delegate permissions"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #128 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS feature or service can be used to capture information about incoming and outgoing traffic in an AWS VPC infrastructure?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Config", "CORRECT:B. VPC Flow Logs", "C. AWS Trusted Advisor", "D. AWS CloudTrail"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/flow-logs.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #129 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company wants to use an AWS service to monitor the health of application endpoints, with the ability to route traffic to healthy regional endpoints to improve application availability. Which service will support these requirements?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Inspector", "B. Amazon CloudWatch", "CORRECT:C. AWS Global Accelerator", "D. Amazon CloudFront"],"explanation": "AWS Global Accelerator uses the AWS global network to optimize the path from your users to your applications, improving the performance of your traffic by as much as 60%. AWS Global Accelerator continually monitors the health of your application endpoints and redirects traffic to healthy endpoints in less than 30 seconds. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/global-accelerator/?blogs-global-accelerator.sort-by=item.additionalFields.createdDate&blogs-global-accelerator.sort- order=desc&aws-global-accelerator-wn.sort-by=item.additionalFields.postDateTime&aws-global-accelerator-wn.sort-order=desc","discussions": "11"}, "Question #130 Topic 2":{ "question":"According to the AWS Well-Architected Framework, what change management steps should be taken to achieve reliability in the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Use AWS Config to generate an inventory of AWS resources", "B. Use service limits to prevent users from creating or making changes to AWS resources", "C. Use AWS CloudTrail to record AWS API calls into an auditable log file", "CORRECT:D. Use AWS Certificate Manager to whitelist approved AWS resources and services", "CORRECT:E. Use Amazon GuardDuty to validate configuration changes made to AWS resources"],"explanation": "","discussions": "10"}, "Question #131 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which service can be used to monitor and receive alerts for AWS account root user AWS Management Console sign-in events?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon CloudWatch", "B. AWS Config", "C. AWS Trusted Advisor", "D. AWS IAM"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/mt/monitor-and-notify-on-aws-account-root-user-activity/","discussions": "5"}, "Question #132 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which design principle should be considered when architecting in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Think of servers as non-disposable resources", "B. Use synchronous integration of services", "CORRECT:C. Design loosely coupled components", "D. Implement the least permissive rules for security groups"],"explanation": "Reference: https://www.botmetric.com/blog/aws-cloud-architecture-design-principles/","discussions": "3"}, "Question #133 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services can be used to move data from on-premises data centers to AWS? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS Snowball", "B. AWS Lambda", "C. AWS ElastiCache", "CORRECT:D. AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)", "E. Amazon API Gateway"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/snowball/","discussions": "2"}, "Question #134 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which methods can be used to identify AWS costs by departments? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Enable multi-factor authentication for the AWS account root user.", "CORRECT:B. Create separate accounts for each department.", "C. Use Reserved Instances whenever possible.", "CORRECT:D. Use tags to associate each instance with a particular department.", "E. Pay bills using purchase orders."],"explanation": "","discussions": "1"}, "Question #135 Topic 2":{ "question":"A batch workload takes 5 hours to finish on an Amazon EC2 instance. The amount of data to be processed doubles monthly and the processing time is proportional. What is the best cloud architecture to address this consistently growing demand?", "answers":[ "A. Run the application on a bigger EC2 instance size.", "B. Switch to an EC2 instance family that better matches batch requirements.", "CORRECT:C. Distribute the application across multiple EC2 instances and run the workload in parallel.", "D. Run the application on a bare metal EC2 instance."],"explanation": "","discussions": "3"}, "Question #136 Topic 2":{ "question":"Each department within a company has its own independent AWS account and its own payment method. New company leadership wants to centralize departmental governance and consolidate payments. How can this be achieved using AWS services or features?", "answers":[ "A. Forward monthly invoices for each account. Then create IAM roles to allow cross-account access.", "B. Create a new AWS account. Then configure AWS Organizations and invite all existing accounts to join.", "CORRECT:C. Configure AWS Organizations in each of the existing accounts. Then link all accounts together.", "D. Use Cost Explorer to combine costs from all accounts. Then replicate IAM policies across accounts."],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_manage_accounts.html","discussions": "4"}, "Question #137 Topic 2":{ "question":"The ability to horizontally scale Amazon EC2 instances based on demand is an example of which concept in the AWS Cloud value proposition?", "answers":[ "A. Economy of scale", "CORRECT:B. Elasticity", "C. High availability", "D. Agility"],"explanation": "","discussions": "2"}, "Question #138 Topic 2":{ "question":"An ecommerce company anticipates a huge increase in web traffic for two very popular upcoming shopping holidays. Which AWS service or feature can be configured to dynamically adjust resources to meet this change in demand?", "answers":[ "A. AWS CloudTrail", "CORRECT:B. Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling", "C. Amazon Forecast", "D. AWS Config"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #139 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service enables users to securely connect to AWS resources over the public internet?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon VPC peering", "B. AWS Direct Connect", "C. AWS VPN", "D. Amazon Pinpoint"],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-security-whitepaper.pdf (36)","discussions": "5"}, "Question #140 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which tool is used to forecast AWS spending?", "answers":[ "A. AWS Trusted Advisor", "B. AWS Organizations", "CORRECT:C. Cost Explorer", "D. Amazon Inspector"],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/ce-forecast.html","discussions": "2"}, "Question #141 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company is running an ecommerce application hosted in Europe. To decrease latency for users who access the website from other parts of the world, the company would like to cache frequently accessed static content closer to the users. Which AWS service will support these requirements?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon ElastiCache", "CORRECT:B. Amazon CloudFront", "C. Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)", "D. Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"],"explanation": "Amazon CloudFront employs a global network of edge locations and regional edge caches that cache copies of your content close to your viewers. Amazon CloudFront ensures that end-user requests are served by the closest edge location. As a result, viewer requests travel a short distance, improving performance for your viewers. For files not cached at the edge locations and the regional edge caches, Amazon CloudFront keeps persistent connections with your origin servers so that those files can be fetched from the origin servers as quickly as possible. Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/faqs/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #142 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following is a component of the AWS Global Infrastructure?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon Alexa", "CORRECT:B. AWS Regions", "C. Amazon Lightsail", "D. AWS Organizations"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #143 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service will help users determine if an application running on an Amazon EC2 instance has sufficient CPU capacity?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon CloudWatch", "B. AWS Config", "C. AWS CloudTrail", "D. Amazon Inspector"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/faqs/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #144 Topic 2":{ "question":"Why is it beneficial to use Elastic Load Balancers with applications?", "answers":[ "A. They allow for the conversion from Application Load Balancers to Classic Load Balancers.", "CORRECT:B. They are capable of handling constant changes in network traffic patterns.", "C. They automatically adjust capacity.", "D. They are provided at no charge to users."],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/latest/userguide/what-is-load-balancing.html","discussions": "4"}, "Question #145 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which tasks are the customer's responsibility in the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Infrastructure facilities access management", "B. Cloud infrastructure hardware lifecycle management", "CORRECT:C. Configuration management of user's applications", "D. Networking infrastructure protection", "CORRECT:E. Security groups configuration"],"explanation": "Reference: https://cloudacademy.com/blog/aws-shared-responsibility-model-security/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #146 Topic 2":{ "question":"IT systems should be designed to reduce interdependencies, so that a change or failure in one component does not cascade to other components. This is an example of which principle of cloud architecture design?", "answers":[ "A. Scalability", "CORRECT:B. Loose coupling", "C. Automation", "D. Automatic scaling"],"explanation": "Reference: https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf (20)","discussions": "1"}, "Question #147 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS service or feature can enhance network security by blocking requests from a particular network for a web application on AWS? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. AWS WAF", "B. AWS Trusted Advisor", "C. AWS Direct Connect", "D. AWS Organizations", "CORRECT:E. Network ACLs"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/waf/ https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/vpc-network-acls.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #148 Topic 2":{ "question":"An application runs on multiple Amazon EC2 instances that access a shared file system simultaneously. Which AWS storage service should be used?", "answers":[ "A. Amazon EBS", "CORRECT:B. Amazon EFS", "C. Amazon S3", "D. AWS Artifact"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/efs/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #149 Topic 2":{ "question":"A web application is hosted on AWS using an Elastic Load Balancer, multiple Amazon EC2 instances, and Amazon RDS. Which security measures fall under the responsibility of AWS? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Running a virus scan on EC2 instances", "B. Protecting against IP spoofing and packet sniffing", "CORRECT:C. Installing the latest security patches on the RDS instance", "CORRECT:D. Encrypting communication between the EC2 instances and the Elastic Load Balancer", "E. Configuring a security group and a network access control list (NACL) for EC2"],"explanation": "","discussions": "4"}, "Question #150 Topic 2":{ "question":"What is the benefit of elasticity in the AWS Cloud?", "answers":[ "A. Ensure web traffic is automatically spread across multiple AWS Regions.", "B. Minimize storage costs by automatically archiving log data.", "C. Enable AWS to automatically select the most cost-effective services.", "CORRECT:D. Automatically adjust the required compute capacity to maintain consistent performance."],"explanation": "Reference: https://aimconsulting.com/insights/blog/the-elastic-cloud-opportunity/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #151 Topic 2":{ "question":"The continual reduction of AWS Cloud pricing is due to:", "answers":[ "A. pay-as-you go pricing", "B. the AWS global infrastructure", "CORRECT:C. economies of scale", "D. reserved storage pricing"],"explanation": "Reference: https://read.acloud.guru/there-are-four-reasons-to-explain-how-using-aws-can-change-the-economic-model-of-the-it-services-850dcc8ea1aa? gi=3bcf6cd0e1e2","discussions": "1"}, "Question #152 Topic 2":{ "question":"A company needs an Amazon S3 bucket that cannot have any public objects due to compliance requirements. How can this be accomplished?", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Enable S3 Block Public Access from the AWS Management Console.", "B. Hold a team meeting to discuss the importance if only uploading private S3 objects.", "C. Require all S3 objects to be manually approved before uploading.", "D. Create a service to monitor all S3 uploads and remove any public uploads."],"explanation": "Reference: https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/access-control-block-public-access.html","discussions": "1"}, "Question #153 Topic 2":{ "question":"A Cloud Practitioner identifies a billing issue after examining the AWS Cost and Usage report in the AWS Management Console. Which action can be taken to resolve this?", "answers":[ "A. Open a detailed case related to billing and submit it to AWS Support for help.", "CORRECT:B. Upload data describing the issue to a new object in a private Amazon S3 bucket.", "C. Create a pricing application and deploy it to a right-sized Amazon EC2 instance for more information.", "D. Proceed with creating a new dashboard in Amazon QuickSight."],"explanation": "","discussions": "5"}, "Question #154 Topic 2":{ "question":"What does the AWS Simple Monthly Calculator do?", "answers":[ "A. Compares on-premises costs to colocation environments", "CORRECT:B. Estimates monthly billing based on projected usage", "C. Estimates power consumption at existing data centers", "D. Estimates CPU utilization"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/estimate-your-c/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #155 Topic 2":{ "question":"Who is responsible for patching the guest operating system for Amazon RDS?", "answers":[ "A. The AWS Product team", "CORRECT:B. The customer Database Administrator", "C. Managed partners", "D. AWS Support"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","discussions": "10"}, "Question #156 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS services may be scaled using AWS Auto Scaling? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "CORRECT:A. Amazon EC2", "CORRECT:B. Amazon DynamoDB", "C. Amazon S3", "D. Amazon Route 53", "E. Amazon Redshift"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/faqs/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #157 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which of the following are benefits of AWS Global Accelerator? (Choose two.)", "answers":[ "A. Reduced cost to run services on AWS", "CORRECT:B. Improved availability of applications deployed on AWS", "C. Higher durability of data stored on AWS", "CORRECT:D. Decreased latency to reach applications deployed on AWS", "E. Higher security of data stored on AWS"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/global-accelerator/faqs/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #158 Topic 2":{ "question":"A user who wants to get help with billing and reactivate a suspended account should submit an account and billing request to:", "answers":[ "A. the AWS Support forum", "B. AWS Abuse", "C. an AWS Solutions Architect", "CORRECT:D. AWS Support"],"explanation": "Reference: https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/knowledge-center/reactivate-suspended-account/","discussions": "1"}, "Question #159 Topic 2":{ "question":"Which AWS Cloud best practice uses the elasticity and agility of cloud computing?", "answers":[ "A. Provision capacity based on past usage and theoretical peaks", "CORRECT:B. Dynamically and predictively scale to meet usage demands", "C. Build the application and infrastructure in a data center that grants physical access", "D. Break apart the application into loosely coupled components"],"explanation": "In a traditional computing environment, you provision capacity based on an estimate of a theoretical maximum peak. This can result in periods where expensive resources are sitting idle or occasions of insufficient capacity. With cloud computing, you can access as much or as little capacity as you need and dynamically scale to meet actual demand, while only paying for what you use.","discussions": "3"}}}